<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bruno Gurgel (@bggo)</title>
    <link>http://brunogurgel.com.br/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Bruno Gurgel (@bggo)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 17:12:21 -0300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://brunogurgel.com.br/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Deploying a personal website</title>
      <link>http://brunogurgel.com.br/posts/personal_website/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 17:12:21 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brunogurgel.com.br/posts/personal_website/</guid>
      <description>Part 1 of 4 - Deciding the stack  After a long time without writing some tech stuff I have decided to put my website/blog back online! Writing here was a fun task to document the process itself. Hope you enjoy.
 Back in time I used to host my own server, either in my home or in the early beginning as a IaaS Machine on the cloud, many times as a shared VPS or a tiny machine where I could have my Debian OS, with Apache as a webserver to run some PHP code using Wordpress.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Runners Tears</title>
      <link>http://brunogurgel.com.br/posts/the-runners-tears/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 14:06:58 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brunogurgel.com.br/posts/the-runners-tears/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever cried during your favorite exercise? This title may sound weird to you. You may think, “Are you ok?”, “Do you need help?”, “Are you injured?” but, wait, I’ll try to make my point over the next few paragraphs.
In “true acceptance” I wrote about my journey, facing all my silent beliefs to start over. Exercises will always be an important part of this life transition. Swimming, skateboarding, cross training and cycling were already part of my life in some way, but running was not.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skills of the Future</title>
      <link>http://brunogurgel.com.br/posts/skills-of-the-future/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 14:06:32 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brunogurgel.com.br/posts/skills-of-the-future/</guid>
      <description>Some thoughts about IT skills in a near future It was not long ago when some of us realized that machines, algorithms and software were pushing us out of our jobs. People started seeing years of study and experience threatened by this new era where digital transformation, like any other revolution, has challenged us to move out of our comfort zones.
The thing is, we need once again to adapt to this new reality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quarantine Little Habits</title>
      <link>http://brunogurgel.com.br/posts/quarantine-little-habits/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 14:06:07 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brunogurgel.com.br/posts/quarantine-little-habits/</guid>
      <description>What I&amp;rsquo;m gonna miss after COVID-19 pandemic crisis It was not long ago when we could walk in the park, shop, hang out with friends or go out for a meal at a great restaurant across the city. We were free to move around and do wherever we wanted without having any idea that a huge pandemic to be caused by COVID-19 was looming.
The nightmare arrived and hit hard everybody’s routines; many of us are now facing a new work reality, in a different environment, with different distractions like family, pets, noises, and even the short distance between our fridge and our workstations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>True Acceptance</title>
      <link>http://brunogurgel.com.br/posts/true-acceptance/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2020 11:39:26 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brunogurgel.com.br/posts/true-acceptance/</guid>
      <description>The journey of constant learning It&amp;rsquo;s been almost 2 year that I decided to give myself a different life. Not a life with limitations, or without the things that gives me most pleasure, materially and spiritually, but a life full of awareness, seeking my true purposes.
I never gave personal habits truly importance. In every single aspect, I didn&amp;rsquo;t have time to stop what I was doing to plan, think or even understand the colateral effects of my daily actions.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>